Guide to A. George Schillinger Papers RG.048
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series V: Brooklyn Poly, 1949-2008
  - Sub-series B: Administrative, 1968-2006
    - Division of Management Overview, 1977-1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Transfer of Computer to AJW, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Executive Technical Development, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Licensing Executives Society, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Routes to Westchester Polytechnic, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Task Force #3, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Division of Management Assignments, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Mgt. Presentation 2, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Kikutake, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - John Haines, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Changes of Address, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Papagiannelis, Peter P., 2001 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Sub-series C: Contracts and Proposals, 1973-2002
    - Argonne Nat'l Lab (Proposal - REJ), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Project Performance Corp. (Contract), 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Sloan Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Carnegie Corporation Proposal, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Bugliarello, George (Center for Tech & Merchandising Proposal), 2002 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Feinsot, A. (NYU Dean), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - NSF Proposal 2002, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Sub-series D: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1962-2004
    - Management, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Management 2, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Technical University of Budapest, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Rod Nichols, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Nichols, R.W., 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Management Correspondence 1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - ISTMP Donation and Payroll, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Management Dept. Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - CHRON File (1988) Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Schillinger (CHRON File, 1985-1987) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - A.G.S. CHRON File (1989) Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - A-B (Correspondence), 1986-2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Battelle Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - C-D (Correspondence), 1987-1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Davidson, Frank P. (Correspondence and Articles on The Channel Tunnel), 1985-1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - I-L (Correspondence), 1982-1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - M-N (Correspondence), 1985-1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Global Education Advisory Board, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Task Force Cluster #3, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - A. G. Schillinger 2 (1969-1970) (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Manuscripts, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Chronological Correspondence (1978-1980) (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Cheryl Ann Robinson Obituary, 2004-05-06 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (1980-1984) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Truxal, John G. Provost, 1962-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - IM - ORSA - SS Interaction Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Management Program, 1977-1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Truxal Letters, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1975-11-25 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - XYZ - Miscellaneous, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres 1997) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres. - 1998) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres) 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres - 2000) (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres) 2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - A. George Schillinger (Corres) 2002 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - A.G. Schillinger Corres (2003) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Ralph E. Weindling (Corres.), 1993-1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - V - Z (Correspondence), 1985-1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres. - 1992) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Schillinger A.G. Correspondence (1991) (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Correspondence - 1990) (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Correspondence, 1989) (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Correspondence 1988) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - S - U (Correspondence), 1984-1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sellers, Wallace O. (Correspondence), 1983-1990 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - A.G. Schillinger (Corres. 1996), 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - A. George Schillinger (1995) Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - A.G. Schillinger (1994) Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Schillinger, A.G. (Corres. - 1993) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Sub-series E: Curriculum, 1950-2006
    - IBM Rel. Course, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - MSTCM Syllabi & Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - MG760: International Development: Management & Technology, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Management Course Revisions, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Management Curriculum Revisions, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Foster Program Outline, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Ph.D Dissertation, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Retail Supply Chain (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Supply Chain Management Correspondence, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - LECCE Executive Workshop, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Cheon, Kangsik, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hangzhou Institute of Elect. Engr. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Electrical Engineering 101 (1965-1966) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Electrical Engineering 101 (1962-1965) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - EE 101 Quizes Fall 1965 Electrical Engineering (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - EE 102 (1963-1966) Electrical Engineering 102, 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Electrical Engineering 102 (1965) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - EE 102 Final Exam Solutions & Student Work (1965) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Oxford Centre for Management Studies (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Management Memorandum, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Management Strategic Plan, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Management 9/92 - Faculty Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Meeting with Professor Elting Morison (1/4/1989), 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - MS in Management of Technology Meeting (1988) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - University of Leece, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - IE941 Issues in Science and Technology, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Strategies for the Engineering and Construction Industry (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Hoffman, Kenneth C. Dissertation, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - IE942 - Fall 1968 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - EE705: Algebraic Codes and Networks, 1965-1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - EE131, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - EE264 Notes - Quizes, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - EE R162, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - The Simulation of Cognitive Processes: An Annotated Bibliography (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - CCNY: EE282, 303, 304 BPI: EE409, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - IE613 - Games, Queries, Inventory, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - EE611, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Determinants (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - EE415 Homework and Quizzes, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - MA151, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - MG600 - Fall '86 - Wschtr, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - MG600: Management Process, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - MG300 Sp '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - MG300 Fall '87, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - MG970 Fall 1988, 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - MG600 Fall '87, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - MG866 Spring '89, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Urban Siting of Nuclear Power Plants - C. Spejenkowski, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - The Computer and the Invasion of Privacy - Leslie Steinherz, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lethal Weapons - RL Honigman (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - The Effect of a System Change to Electric Vehicles - A Policy Study (Aniko Giordano) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - MG865, MG866, MG975, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - MG866, MG970, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - MOT Schedule & Course Descriptions (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - National Health Policy - Edward B. Gomeau, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Revised Term Paper Outline - Albert Talerico (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Electromag Notes, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Networks Notes, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Transients Notes, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Electronics Notes, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - EE 961 Report Project, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - EE 701 (B) Exams & Problems, 1959-1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Master Program Information & Harvard Business School, 1980-1990 (Box 13, Item 1)
  - Sub-series F: Evaluations, 1993-1999
    - Surveys (May 1999) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Jan Rosenbaum Spring '97 (Course Evaluation), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - AGS Student Evaluation, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Management Course Evaluations (1997) (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Management Course Evaluations (1996) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Management Course Evaluations (1995) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sub-series G: Events and Conferences, 1980-1995
    - National Conference for Deans, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Board on Science and Technology for International Development Meeting, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - The NY Academy of Sciences, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Supercomm '92/ICC, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - NYAS Meeting Dates, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Sub-series H: Faculty and Student Employment, 1966-2004
    - CV G. Schillinger, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - John Charles Auerbach CV (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Danzinger, Michael Roy CV, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Greenstein, Michael, P.E. CV (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Robert Maciag, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Recommendations, 1988-2003 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Benson, Yair, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Rao, Bharat, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Ziv, Nina, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Mel Horwitch, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Resumes 1, 1994-1999 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Resumes 2, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Search Committee Mgt 1996, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Search Committee (2), 1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Dr. Lemuel Tarshis, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - A. George Schillinger (CV), 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mel Horwitch - Corres., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Institute/Mel, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Mel - Advanced Management Learning Initiative, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Horwitch, Mel CV, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Ralph E. Weindling, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Bostic, Cynthia, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Lemuel Tarshis, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Willett, Martha, 1976-1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Denson, Darlene, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Mark Preuss, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Tak Kwan Mok, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Chau Nguyen, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Cheuk-Hung Tam, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Second Screening - 1992 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - David Lewis, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Positions in Technology Management, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Employment Applications (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Applied/Interviewed - No, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Acker, Juliette, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Position in Technology MGT, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Evaluations of Candidates, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Search for Management of Technology Dept., 2004 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Faculty Search for Management of Technology Dept. (2002) (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Graham Mitchell, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Monti, Ricardo, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Nasmith, Jr. Augustus, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Applications - Adm. Aide, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Palocz Reference for NYU Tenure, 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Cheryl Robinson, 1988-2003 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Ralph E. Weindling Harvard Honorary Dinner, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Darius Sabavala CV, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Sub-series I: Financial, 1971-2003
    - Vouchers, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Corporate Express Documents, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Panasonic Fax Machine Invoices, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - IBM PC (Personal Computer), 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Hertz Payments, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Furniture & Equipment, 1985-1999 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Vouchers 3, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Special Programs Budget (1971-1975) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Micron - Cablevision, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers 1, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers 2, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Computer Purchase, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers 87-88, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Financial Reports Inquiry Forms, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sub-series J: Grants and Awards, 1975-2008
    - Lydia Ryabova Research Scholarship, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - The John D. & Catherine T. Macarthur Foundation, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Grants, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Foundations & Grants 2002 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Kent State - Application for Travel Grant, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Prof. George Schillinger Award 2001-2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - New York Academy of Sciences Mayor's Award, 1996-2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - NYAS Mayor's Award Correspondence 1, 1992-2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - NYAS Mayor's Award Correspondence 2, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - NYAS Mayor's Award 1997 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Mayor's Awards in Sci & Tech (2003) (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Mayor's Award (2001) (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence (2001-2002) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Weber Project, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - (FAS Reports) Grant Budget Status, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series K: Marketing and Publications, 1991-2003
    - The Chronicle of Higher Education (Articles re: Poly), 2003 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Delta Sky, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Beekman Enterprises, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Sub-series L: Nominations, 1989-1993
    - Distinguished Teacher Award, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Sub-series M: Program Development, 1969-1975
    - Development Program for Polytechnic, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Forecasting Committee, Task Force 3, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - IBM Mid-Hudson Valley, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Sub-series N: Research and Reports, 1968-1999
    - A. G. Schillinger (Speeches), 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Study, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - New Directions in Continuing Education: Changing Roles of Universities, Industry and Government (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - "Man's Changing View of Nature: The Roots of our Modern Manipulative Attitude" (Schillinger) (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - "Studying the Future: A New Discipline" (Schillinger), 1968-03 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Mid-Hudson (IBM) Study, 1969-03 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - "Man's Changing View of Nature" Copies (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Ratchford, J. Thomas S&T Policy, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Sub-series O: Seminars and Lectures, 1949-1999
    - Probability Lecture (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Probability Lecture Notes (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Arnaldo Angelini, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Managing Technology: Corporate Perspective, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Executive Seminar in Technology Management, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Advanced Technology Management (Promotion) 1, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Advanced Technology Management (Promotion) 2, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Advanced Technology Management (Correspondence), 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Advanced Technology Management (Promotion) 3, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - ATM Promotion/Originals (1984) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - ATM Budget (1984) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Advanced Technology Management Announcement, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - NATO Conference (1994) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - NATO Conference (1996) (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - NYAS - Distance Learning, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Information Theory Seminar, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Servo-Anal. Comp. - 261, 1952-1957 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Direct Current Machinery Laboratory, 1949 (Box 16, Item 1)
    - Sabavala, Darius, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Advanced Technology Management 1, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Advanced Technology Management 2, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Macro-Engineering Course, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Aurelio Peccei, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 1967/68 Seminar (Interdisciplinary), 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Continuing Education of Engineers Seminar - Helsinki, Finland August 1972, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Lecture on Error-Correcting Codes, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Advanced Technology Seminar (1983), 1979-1983 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Advanced Technology Management Correspondence, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Morison, Elting, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Kearfott - Error Detection and Correction Coding Notes, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - ATM Mailing Lists (1983) 1, 1982-1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - ATM Mailing Lists (1983) 2, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - ATM Seminar, Spring 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Series VI: Societies, Conferences, and Committees, 1968-2002
  - Sub-series A: American Automatic Control Council, 1970-1975
    - JACC 1974 AACC Committee on Social Effects of Automation, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - AACC1972-JACC Session Incl. Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - AACC Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - AACC Com. on Social Effects of Automation (Minutes, Membership Lists, Notes), 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Sub-series B: Associations, 1968-2002
    - Major Projects Association Members and Representatives, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Canadian Major Projects Assoc., 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Public Education Association (1968-1969) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series C: Committees, 1976-1999
    - Carnegie Commission (David Z. Robinson), 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Committee, 1976-11-23 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Paris/New York Transatlantic (June 9/10/1999) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sub-series D: Conferences, 1969-1993
    - Vouchers and Registration Form (ASEE Annual Conference 1981) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Mega Cities, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Jonathan Plaut, EC Hungarian Environmental Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Buenos Aires & Salvador (1981-1983) (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Operating Manual for the Joint Automatic Control Conference, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Nat'l Academy of Sci/Hungarian Academy of Sci Conf. 12/7-9/92, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - New York TECHSCAN Agenda, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Southern Sociological Society Conference (Content and Correspondence), 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Technology Forecast for 1980 Symposium), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Weizmann Institute of Science Forum, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Content & Expenses (World-Wide Armed Forces Education Conf.), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Sub-series E: National Research Council, 1987-2000
    - NRC (2000) Travel Grant Applications, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - NRC/AID Mtg 3/14/88, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Nat'l Research Council - G. Schweitzer, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - AID Workshop March 14-15, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series F: Science, Technology, and Society, 1987-2002
    - STS Encyclopedia, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - STS Encyclopedia 2, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Carl Mitcham, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - STS Encyclopedia 1 (1977-1987) (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - STS Encyclopedia Correspondence (1987-1989) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Sub-series G: Societies, 1992-1994
    - LES Annual Report, Journal, and Meeting, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Sub-series H: United Nations, 1978-1979
    - UN Forum on Science & Technology for Devel., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - UN Conference on Science & Technology for Devel., 1979 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - UNESCO Study Grants, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 30)